Episode 8
第8集
Young Master, even though you are a woman...
少爷，虽然你是个女人……
i know...
我知道...
Human life is only once.
人的生命只有一次。
Even if there are bad intentions...
哪怕有恶意...
I will not risk my life.
我不会冒生命危险。
What does it mean?
这是什么意思？
We had a therapist today.
今天我们有一位治疗师。
Isn't that because you want to check...
是不是因为你想检查...
Are my injuries real?
我的伤是真的吗？
I know you are biased against me.
我 知道你对我有偏见。
But Dr. Wu also said this.
但吴博士也说过这样的话。
That arrow could kill me.
那支箭可以杀死我。
So I'm afraid of pain...
所以我很怕痛...
I use perfume to brighten it up.
我 用香水来提亮它。
Do you still think I'm not afraid of death?
你还以为我不怕死吗？
At the ancestral rite...
祭祖仪式上...
I don't know what I did...
我不知道我做了什么...
Until you have doubts.
直到你有疑问为止。
But more than anything, I'm worried about your safety.
但最重要的是，我担心你的安全。
in my life.
在我生命中。
Isn't that enough to prove my sincerity ?
这还不足以证明我的诚意吗 ？
I said something wrong.
我说错话了。
Young master. ma'am.
少爷。女士。
Your servant Mu Yao has arrived.
奴婢沐瑶来了。
Was that the player you beat last time?
那是你上次击败的玩家吗？
Yes, Young Master. That's me.
是的，少爷。这就是我。
I heard that Master came to visit...
听说师父来访了……
So he asked me to invite you .
所以他让我邀请你 。
rest well
好好休息
I won't bother you.
我不会打扰你。
ma'am.
女士。
Madam, is your wound very painful?
女士，您的伤口很痛吗？
Your eyes are red.
你的眼睛是红色的。
yes. It really hurts.
是的。真的很疼。
Would you like to add some scent?
您想添加一些香味吗？
no.
不。
Get rid of it from now on.
从现在开始摆脱它。
Aren’t you afraid of getting sick, ma’am?
女士，您不怕生病吗？
As Dr. Woo said...
正如吴博士所说...
If you overuse this sleeping perfume...
如果你过度使用这款睡眠香水......
It will ruin your mind.
它会毁掉你的思想。
From now on, no matter how painful it is...
从现在开始， 无论多痛苦……
I won't use it.
我不会用它。
I can't lose my mind anymore.
我不能再失去理智了。
Somehow...
不知何故...
Some people can do it easily...
有些人可以轻松做到...
Earns the love and trust of others .
赢得他人的爱戴和信任。
With just one look...
只要一看...
Other people will fall in love with them too.
其他人也会爱上他们。
As for other people...
至于其他人……
People who worked hard...
那些努力工作的人...
I'm still receiving hostility and suspicion.
我仍然受到敌意 和怀疑。
Despite trying hard...
尽管很努力...
And it doesn't look any different than before.
而且看上去和以前并没有什么不同。
Madam, who are you talking about?
女士，您在说谁？
ma'am.
女士。
The teacher said he was busy...
老师说他很忙...
So I couldn't come.
所以我没能来。
Where are all the bodies?
所有的尸体都在哪里？
The hostess is confined to her bed...
女主人被困在床上……
And Master hasn't visited yet...
师父还没有来过……
So the employees started to become lazy.
于是，员工们开始变得懒惰起来。
Madam, why don't you come inside...
夫人，您怎么不进来……
Then shall I sort it out?
那我要整理一下吗？
ma'am.
女士。
Your sister sent you some more jewelry.
你姐姐又给你送了一些珠宝。
Didn't I tell you to stop it?
我不是叫你停下来了吗？
My cupboard is almost full.
我的橱柜快满了。
already.
已经。
But he didn't listen.
但他不听。
That person keeps sending me things...
那个人一直给我发东西...
But I've never visited it.
但我从来没有参观过它。
He visited your mother this morning.
他今天早上拜访了你的母亲。
but...
但...
what?
什么？
That's just...
那只是...
It's just that the master blocked it ...
只是被主人挡住了 ……
And that seems to tell them something...
这似乎告诉了他们一些事情......
So they are afraid to come back.
所以他们害怕回来。
ma'am.
女士。
Are you going out?
你出门吗？
I'm going to meet Jong Ye-ran.
我要去见钟艺兰。
I need to talk to the teacher.
我需要和老师谈谈。
Please tell him I am here.
请告诉他我在这里。
The teacher said...
老师说...
He doesn't want to see you.
他不想见你。
But there is something I really want to say to him .
但有件事我真的很想对他说 。
Mu Yao.
穆瑶。
Like I said before...
正如我之前所说...
Now I don't have much choice...
现在我已经没有太多选择了...
But I no longer...
但我不再...
Having bad intentions towards you.
对你怀有恶意。
I promise...
我保证...
I will repay the debt I owe you little by little.
我会一点一点地偿还欠你的债。
Can you trust me just once?
你能相信我一次吗？
I am working ...
我在工作 ...
And I don't have time to meet anyone.
而且我没有时间去见任何人。
Ah, Hua Chen...
啊，华晨……
I'm here to ask for a divorce.
我是来请求离婚的。
What did I say...
我说了什么...
This was done after careful consideration.
这是经过深思熟虑后做出的。
I hope the teacher takes this seriously.
希望老师认真对待这件事。
I will go and wait for your answer.
我 去等你的答复。
Two stupid women.
两个傻女人。
Everyone, why are you so sad?
大家，为何如此悲伤？
I have my own plans.
我有自己的计划。
are you okay.
你还好吗。
Do you think I'll be bullied?
你觉得我会被欺负吗？
Kuiju, eat some snacks.
魁菊，吃点零食吧。
I didn't eat breakfast.
我没吃早餐。
I can't even walk properly anymore .
我什至无法正常行走了 。
I think I'm too shameless again.
我想我又太无耻了。
Madam, are you okay?
女士，您还好吗？
Young man, you are promising.
年轻人，你很有前途。
You are a young man...
你是个年轻人...
The person who saved me...
那个救了我的人...
It's during ancestral rites, right ?
是在祭祖的时候吧 ？
ma'am.
女士。
Yeah that's me
是啊，那是我
I couldn't hear you clearly at that time.
当时我听不清楚。
What is your name?
你叫什么名字？
My Name...
我的名字...
Huarongzhou.
华容洲。
How dare you look at your wife...
你怎么敢看你老婆……
Chenz!
陈兹！
You saved my life.
你救了我的命。
I will remember your name.
我会记住你的名字。
Coincidentally, our last names are the same.
巧合的是，我们的姓氏相同。
I think we were destined to meet.
我想我们是命中注定的相遇。
How old are you?
你今年多大？
I am 16 years old.
我16岁。
Then I am older than you.
那 我比你大。
I am one year older. Yes, I am 17 years old.
我又大一岁了。 是的，我今年 17 岁。
I will remember that you saved my life.
我 会记住你救了我的命。
fag.
基佬。
Thank you so much, ma'am.
非常感谢你，女士。
Young Master, about the attack...
少爷，关于袭击事件……
I looked at it several times...
我看了好几遍...
And I noticed something suspicious.
我注意到一些可疑的事情。
what?
什么？
last year...
去年...
All traces of the Ge family have been erased...
葛家的一切痕迹都被抹去了……
And they never showed up.
他们从未出现。
That didn't stop the investigation.
这并没有阻止调查。
After all, people here still hate them...
毕竟，这里的人 还是讨厌他们……
Because they use fake, low-quality fragrances.
因为他们使用假冒伪劣香水。
To harm people.
去害人。
Once they know...
一旦他们知道...
They will report this to the authorities.
他们 将向当局报告此事。
It can be done...
可以办到...
If only there were a few of Ge's men...
要是有几个葛家的人就好了……
Who is hiding here?
谁躲在这里？
But, there is no way...
但是，没有办法……
Suddenly a group of people will appear.
突然就会出现一群人。
Is it true?
这是真的吗？
I felt attacked...
我感觉受到了攻击...
The goal is to steal our secret formula.
我们的目标是窃取我们的秘密配方。
The crab family and the middle family...
蟹家族和中家族……
That's how strong it is.
就是这么强。
Besides that...
除此之外...
Who else would dare attack?
还有谁敢进攻？
The attacker...
攻击者...
Maybe he's from the Ge family.
也许他是葛家的人。
Maybe there are people...
也许有人...
In our city...
在我们的城市...
It helps cover their tracks ...
它有助于掩盖他们的踪迹 ......
So many of them...
他们中的很多人...
You can stay here without being detected.
你可以呆在这里而不被发现。
Or someone...
或者某人...
On the other hand, please help them...
另一方面，请帮助他们...
So they can sneak into the city quickly.
这样他们 就可以快速潜入城市。
That means...
这意味着...
There are traitors hiding in the city...
城里藏着叛徒……
Or was it the work of an outsider?
还是外人的杰作？
Our guards will work harder to find...
我们的警卫 会更加努力地寻找...
And patrolling...
还有巡逻...
To find the culprit.
去寻找罪魁祸首。
My Lord and Majesty can be sure of that.
陛下和陛下 可以确信这一点。
I'll talk about this with my mom ...
我会和我妈妈讨论这件事 ...
But I suggest...
但我建议...
Don't increase the guards...
不增加警卫...
Except for the gates.
除了城门之外。
Make sure the intensity stays the same.
确保强度保持不变。
How do I know?
我怎么知道？
What if we don’t increase the number of security guards?
如果我们不增加保安人数怎么办？
The feast is about to begin.
盛宴即将开始。
At this important moment...
在这个重要时刻...
We can't lose face...
我们不能丢脸...
In front of merchants outside the city.
城外的商贾面前。
In the end , there weren't many casualties...
最终并 没有造成太多人员伤亡……
And now society is watching us.
现在社会正在注视着我们。
I wonder what I should do now...
我想知道我现在应该做什么...
To convince people...
为了说服人们...
And be quiet and watchful...
并 保持安静和警惕......
Instead of adding a controller...
而不是添加控制器...
It can actually cause panic.
它实际上会 引起恐慌。
But in the case of Mr. Ge's family...
但 就葛先生一家而言……
It's causing a lot of trouble...
给大家带来了很多麻烦...
And many people have been harmed by their actions.
许多 人因他们的行为而受到伤害。
Muda Muda is very attentive.
穆达穆达非常细心。
Young Master.
少爷。
What is that?
那是什么？
When I was busy just now...
刚才我忙的时候...
Chairman Lin left a message.
林董事长留言。
What is it?
它是什么？
Mrs. Hua wants a divorce.
华太太要离婚。
Are you divorced?
你离婚了？
Teacher, it's meal time now.
老师，吃饭时间到了。
Tuan?
团？
I see you eat too little...
我看你吃的太少了...
So I cooked this as a gift for you.
所以我 做了这个作为礼物送给你。
I hope you enjoy it...
我希望你喜欢它...
And you can understand the intention behind this gift.
你也能明白这份礼物背后的用意。
I think my teacher is the only person in my life.
我想我的老师是我生命中唯一的人。
So anyway...
所以无论如何...
I want to be too...
我也想成为...
In his eyes, you are the only one.
在他眼里，你是唯一的。
My love for him is very great...
我对他的爱是非常伟大的...
Until you understand...
直到你明白...
I will do anything to make him happy.
我 会做任何事让他开心。
Ah, Hua Chen...
啊，华晨……
I'm here to ask for a divorce.
我是来请求离婚的。
What I said...
我所说...
This was done after careful consideration.
这是经过深思熟虑后做出的。
I hope the teacher takes this seriously.
希望老师认真对待这件事。
Your wife's hair is already dry.
你妻子的头发已经干了。
Madam, you need to treat your wounds...
女士，您需要处理一下伤口……
And sleep early.
并且早点睡觉。
How old is Hua Rongzhou?
华容舟几岁了？
Do you work here?
你在这工作吗？
Almost a month.
快一个月了。
Does your wife think there is something wrong with him?
你老婆 觉得他有什么问题吗？
of.
的。
What is that?
那是什么？
He is very handsome.
他非常帅。
We have a regular security guard at our house...
我们家有固定的保安...
With such a beautiful face...
拥有如此美丽的容颜……
And the same last name as me.
而且和我同姓。
But I don't remember seeing it.
但我不记得见过它。
ma'am.
女士。
- I heard what you did... - Lee Hine.
- 我听到你做了什么... - 李海因。
Is my father cheating on me?
我的父亲在欺骗我吗？
What do you mean, madam?
女士，您是什么意思？
Or maybe you have an illegitimate child...
或者也许你有一个私生子......
Abandoned?
弃？
Head Steward Hua was an honest man.
华管家 是个老实人。
He cared only about business.
他只关心生意。
He has never taken a concubine.
他从来没有纳过妾。
How could he do such a thing?
他怎么 能做出这样的事？
Then what about my sister?
那么我妹妹呢？
ma'am.
女士。
How can you guess...
你怎么能猜到...
Is this like this about your family?
你的家人也是这样吗？
Young Master is only 23 years old.
少爷才二十三岁。
He is still a child!
他还是个孩子啊！
ma'am...
女士...
I think he's not in a good mood today .
我觉得他今天心情不太好 。
It has to stop.
它必须停止。
ma'am.
女士。
Eat the soup while it is hot.
趁热喝汤。
I think it would be best for you to go to bed early, wife.
我认为你最好早点睡觉，妻子。
Don't think much.
别想太多。
Please take good care of him.
请好好照顾他。
After all, he didn't look like an ordinary person.
毕竟，他 看起来不像是一个普通人。
Madam, go to bed early.
夫人，早点睡吧。
There are a lot of good-looking people around here .
这附近有很多好看的人 。
Please take care of your health.
请注意您的健康。
Don't think too much about it.
别想太多。
correct.
正确的。
In the end, this situation...
到最后，这个情况……
It's different from the past.
这与过去不同了。
It wouldn't be strange if I met someone...
如果我遇到一个人，那也就不奇怪了……
This is someone I have never met .
这是我从未见过的人 。
Just forget it.
把它忘了吧。
It looks pretty valuable...
看起来还蛮值钱的...
But it looks very complicated.
但看起来非常复杂。
Put it on your head...
把它戴在头上...
This will make your throat sore and irritated.
这 会让你的喉咙疼痛和发炎。
I have to sell it tomorrow...
明天我得卖掉它...
And I saved money.
我省了钱。
There is more as far as I remember.
据我所知还有更多。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Packaged.
包装好的。
Light a candle.
点燃一支蜡烛。
Teacher, why are you here?
老师，你怎么来了？
The servants did not say that the Lord was coming.
仆人们并没有说主来了。
Are you coming...
你来吗...
Would you like to get the answer to my question?
您想得到我问题的答案吗？
You thought I was going to kick you out, right?
你以为我会把你赶出去，对吗？
Until you start packing, right?
直到你开始收拾行李，对吗？
It's not like that.
不像那样。
I can not sleep...
我无法入睡...
And I thought...
我想...
I have never seen...
我从来没见过...
Jewelry sent by my sister...
姐姐送的首饰...
So I got up to check it out.
于是我就起身去看看。
In that case...
在这种情况下...
Don't ever try to read my mind again.
永远不要再试图读懂我的想法。
The future?
未来？
what?
什么？
Are you in a hurry to leave?
你急着离开吗？
No, I just...
不，我只是...
Something has been confusing lately .
最近 有些事情让人困惑。
Did you save me from the ancestral rite?
你把我从祭祖仪式中救出来了吗？
Just to make up for your mistakes...
只为弥补你的过错...
Then leave?
然后离开了？
Why do you say that, sir?
先生为什么这么说？
My love for you is so sincere...
我对你的爱是那么的真诚...
And no one has the right to judge me.
而且没有人有权利评判我。
But I overcame it...
但我克服了它...
With my obsession.
带着我的痴迷。
Once my mind becomes clear...
一旦我的思绪变得清晰……
I need to ask for a divorce from you...
我要向你提出离婚...
great. Because you love me so much...
伟大的。 因为你太爱我了...
I will make your wish come true..
我会让你的愿望实现..
And let you stay.
并让你留下来。
That's not a good idea.
这不是一个好主意。
I made a lot of mistakes.
我 犯了很多错误。
- I can't forgive... - Admitting mistakes is a good thing.
- 我无法原谅... - 承认错误是件好事。
You almost died to save me...
你为了救我差点死了……
And I am not an ungrateful person .
而且我也不是一个忘恩负义的人 。
Besides, my house...
另外，我家...
You can support lazy people.
你可以支持懒人。
Sir, it is not what you think .
先生，事情不是你想的那样 。
I can't...
我不能...
Keeps you away.
让你远离。
Your father is the deacon here.
你父亲是这里的执事。
I too must protect his honor.
我也 必须保护他的荣誉。
If you're really sorry...
如果你真的很抱歉...
You can make up for your mistakes...
你可以弥补你的错误...
The future...
未来...
Staying here...
住在这里...
And live a peaceful life.
并过着平静的生活。
Sir, you are the authority here...
先生，您是这里的权威……
And my father is just a butler.
而我的父亲只是一名管家。
Tuan...
团...
Tuan?
团？
Teacher, you can go...
老师，您可以走了……
By the way, can you light a candle?
顺便问一下，你能点蜡烛吗？
I can't see anything.
我什么也看不见。
Sir, I'm not kidding.
先生，我不是在开玩笑。
I really can't see anything .
我真的什么也看不见 。
Tuan?
团？
Jong Ye-ran.
钟艺兰.
You are ungrateful and inhumane.
你忘恩负义 ，毫无人性。
Qianzhi didn't close the window?
千纸没有关窗？
That's not important. I won't freeze.
那不重要。 我不会冻结。
If you close the window...
如果你关上窗户...
I think I'll probably bump into it a few more times.
我想我可能还会碰到它几次。
Ji waiter.
姬侍者。
This is your business.
这是你的事。
Don't leave it to me.
别把它留给我。
Master told me to do so.
师父叫我这样做。
How dare I do something like that?
我怎么敢做这样的事？
But I have to give it to you.
但我 必须把它给你。
Or you have to do it yourself.
或者你必须自己做。
It's a hassle to go back and forth.
来回很麻烦。
That's not important. I don't care.
那不重要。我不在乎。
Hey, G!
嘿，G！
Why are you so cruel?
你为何如此残忍？
You actually let go.
你其实已经 放手了。
Hey, didn't you always like me...?
喂，你不是一直都喜欢我吗……？
Are you going to your wife's residence?
你要去你妻子的住处吗？
This is a great opportunity.
这是一个很好的机会。
You're the one. how?
你是唯一。如何？
That's none of my business. I can't stand it.
那不关我的事。 我受不了了。
Hello, G.
你好，G.
Listen to me.
听我说。
The servants who work for that person...
为那个人工作的仆人......
He always frowns when he sees me.
当他看到我时，他总是皱起眉头。
If I go there again today...
如果我今天再去那里...
I'm afraid they will kick me out.
我担心他们会把我赶出去。
As an honorable person...
作为一个有尊严的人...
And the guard commander...
还有警卫队长……
How can you be so anxious ?
你怎么能这么着急呢 ？
When I see you. You're still young...
当我看见你时。你还年轻...
Also handsome.
也很帅。
Those servants will be happy...
那些仆人会很高兴...
When I see you.
当我看见你时。
Hey, G!
嘿，G！
ji!
吉！
Why do you want to take it?
你为什么要拿它？
you told me
你告诉过我
so? We are at the lady's house.
所以？我们在女士家。
He suffered serious injuries.
他受了重伤。
Let the Lord himself come.
让主亲自来吧。
Nona Chenz.
诺娜·陈兹.
If he does that...
如果他那样做的话……
It would definitely be very awkward.
肯定会非常尴尬。
why?
为什么？
There is no good reason in this world ...
这个世界上 没有什么充分的理由...
Why does the husband treat his wife so coldly?
为什么丈夫 对妻子如此冷漠？
It really is.
确实如此。
Is there a storm brewing early in the morning?
一大早就有暴风雨在酝酿吗？
Qianzhi.
Qianzhi.
ma'am.
女士。
What is that?
那是什么？
Nanfeng comes and says he will...
南风来了，说他会……
tell the truth
说实话
They told me to get rid of it...
他们告诉我要摆脱它......
Home cleanliness sign.
家庭清洁标志。
Madam, you're still injured...
夫人，你还受伤了……
But Master is not interested in your kindness .
但师父对你的好意不感兴趣 。
Just give it to him.
就给他吧。
But you've just started taking on household chores...
但你刚刚开始承担家务......
And I don't fully understand how you can do it ...
我不完全明白你怎么能做到这一点 ......
I studied...
我学...
Do not occupy Zhong's residence.
不侵占钟氏住宅。
Because you already know the process of managing a house...
因为您已经了解管理房屋的流程......
no difference...
没有不同...
Whether I'm holding that sign or not.
不管我是否举着那个牌子。
Besides, I don't care about their money.
再说了，我也不在乎他们的钱。
But ma'am, how could you...
可是，夫人， 你怎么可以……
Qianzhi.
Qianzhi.
Zhong Yelan knows the truth about the temple...
钟夜兰知道了寺庙的真相……
And the plan I made to marry her .
还有我制定的娶她的计划 。
But the lady protected him from the arrows...
但这位女士 保护了他免受箭矢的伤害......
And I almost died.
而我差点就死了。
He couldn't be that cruel, could he?
他不可能这么残忍吧？
If anyone...
如果有人...
Who tricked me into believing his lies...
谁让我 相信了他的谎言……
All day...
一整天...
How should I treat him ?
我该如何对待他 ？
Who dares deceive you, madam?
夫人，谁敢骗您？
I will teach him a lesson.
我会教训他的。
Now in Jong Yeran's eyes...
现在在钟夜然的眼里……
I am that kind of person.
我就是这样的人。
So even though he was given arrows to protect him...
所以 即使他被赋予了箭来保护他......
That doesn't change the facts...
这并不能改变事实...
About what happened in the past.
关于过去发生的事情。
This is what I understand now.
这就是我现在的理解。
Please give Nan Feng an autograph.
请给南风签名。
Okay, ma'am.
好的，女士。
this.
这。
Satisfied?
使满意？
Teacher Qianzhi, please listen to me.
千之老师，请听我说。
Quiet. No need to explain anything.
安静的。 无需解释任何事情。
Don't come here again.
不要再来这里了。
You are a jinx.
你是个恶棍。
Every time I see you something bad happens.
每次我见到你都会有不好的事情发生。
Nona Chenz...
诺娜·陈兹...
- Teacher Qianzhi... - Get out of here.
- 千之老师... - 离开这里。
- Mr. Chenz. - Didn't you hear?
- 陈茨先生。 - 你没听到吗？
He doesn't want to see you.
他不想见你。
- Changan Gangukami - Nonachenji...
- 长安江神 - 野那辰寺...
Unhappiness! You always bring bad luck!
不幸！你总是带来霉运！
- Enyala! - Chenz...
- 恩雅拉！ - 陈兹...
go!
去！
lose one's way!
迷失方向！
How did this happen?
这怎么发生的？
My wife is talking about divorce...
老婆说要离婚了
In front of many servants and subordinates...
当着众多仆人和下属的面……
At the servant’s residence that day...
那天在仆人的住处……
Now almost everyone knows.
现在 几乎所有人都知道了。
Qian didn't like it at first, but...
钱一 开始并不喜欢，但是……
That person is not someone...
那个人不是一个人……
Frustrating...
令人沮丧...
And Yelan is not an irrational person .
而夜阑也不是一个没有理智的人 。
What's wrong with them?
他们怎么了？
Maybe he realized...
也许他意识到...
If you don't marry the person you want...
如果你没有嫁给你想要的人...
And the woman felt like she had married the wrong man...
女人 感觉自己嫁错了男人……
So there was a rift in both of them.
于是 两人之间就产生了裂痕。
they got married
他们结了婚
How could they take this matter lightly?
他们 怎能对这件事掉以轻心？
Send someone there...
派人去那里...
We invite Hua Qian tomorrow.
明天我们请华谦。
I want to ask...
我想问一下...
What happened between them?
他们之间发生了什么？
great. majesty.
伟大的。威严。
wait.
等待。
These few days...
这几天...
He may still be recovering.
他可能仍在康复中。
Just wait 5 more days...
再等5天就好了
Then send someone to invite him or her.
然后派人去 邀请他或她。
good.
好的。
Qianzhi?
Qianzhi?
Insing?
英辛？
Kuiju?
奎聚？
Server Lee?
李服务员？
Where are all the bodies?
所有的尸体都在哪里？
Hello, madam.
你好女士。
Why are you the only bodyguard here?
为什么这里只有你一个保镖？
Housing lacking people...
房子缺人...
So I am the only one who takes care of this place.
所以我是唯一一个照顾这个地方的人。
What about my men?
我的男人们呢？
The servants went to collect.
仆人们就去收拾了。
You need it every day.
你每天都需要它。
Are they all gone? What about the rest?
他们都走了吗？ 剩下的呢？
Housing lacking people...
房子缺人...
So recently...
那么最近...
Some of your men...
你的一些男人...
Sent elsewhere to help .
派往其他地方帮忙 。
There used to be no shortage of people.
以前不缺人。
But after the relationship with Zhong Yeran broke down...
但 和钟野然关系破裂后……
Only then will there be deficiency.
只有这样，才会有不足。
great.
伟大的。
That means there's no need to...
这意味着没有必要...
I remember many names now.
我现在记得很多名字。
Because everyone went...
因为大家都去了...
Why are you still here?
你为什么还在这儿？
I am appointed to serve you...
我被任命为您服务...
So of course you are my priority.
所以你当然是我的首要任务。
I have to say this.
我必须这么说。
Teacher and I will never meet again...
我和老师 再也不会见面了……
So there is no future here .
所以这里没有未来 。
Find another job while you're still young.
趁你还年轻，再找一份工作。
Madam, why are you outside?
夫人，您怎么在外面？
I didn't see anyone inside ...
我没看到里面有人 ...
So I set out to find you.
于是我就出发去找你。
I went to get your food.
我去给你拿食物了。
You can eat now.
你现在可以吃了。
Why should I take it?
我为什么要接受它？
The chef used to bring it here.
厨师曾经把它带到这里。
I understand. Aren’t they short of people?
我明白。 他们不缺人吗？
The chef ordered...
厨师点了...
To reduce household expenses...
为了减少家庭开支...
So that leaves us with this dish.
这样我们就剩下这道菜了。
That's not important. At least we still have two dishes left.
那不重要。至少 我们还剩下两道菜。
When I was living in exile...
当我流亡海外时...
Where have you been?
你去哪儿了？
I went to buy you new clothes.
我去给你买新衣服了。
Chief waiter Ji said.
季总侍说道。
Master, I ordered you to reduce your spending.
主人， 我命令你减少开支。
So you won't get a wife...
那你就娶不到老婆了
Another new clothes.
又是一件新衣服。
That's not important. I have enough clothes...
那不重要。 我的衣服够多了...
For my use.
供我使用。
ma'am.
女士。
What did you get?
你得到了什么？
Housekeepers are outrageous.
管家 真是无耻。
They say that Master ordered them to reduce their spending...
他们说师父命令他们减少开支……
And they just gave me this cheap scent.
他们只是给了我这种廉价的气味。
That's not important. I will not use it from now on.
那不重要。 从现在开始我不会使用它。
Anyway, I don't like it...
反正我是不喜欢...
What they produce.
他们生产什么。
Next time, I will make it myself.
下次我自己做。
say. Master, I ordered you to reduce your spending.
说。主人， 我命令你减少开支。
And what has shrunk now?
现在缩小了什么？
Please take a look at this.
请看一下这个。
This is too much!
这太多了！
He even lowered the quality of the walnuts.
他甚至 降低了核桃的品质。
Walnuts are good for your brain.
核桃对你的大脑有好处。
How will he compensate me if I become stupid?
如果我变傻了，他怎么补偿我？
ma'am...
女士...
Walnuts may look small, but they are edible.
核桃虽然看起来很小，但其实 是可以吃的。
- That's right, ma'am. - no!
- 是的，夫人。 - 不！
relax...
放松...
ma'am.
女士。
I can't argue with Tuan anymore .
我不能再和Tuan争论了 。
After all, you still live in his house.
毕竟 你还住在他家里。
sit down.
坐下。
great.
伟大的。
He ordered spending to be reduced, right?
他 下令减少开支，对吗？
If so, I'll go out and buy mine.
如果是这样，我就出去 买我的。
Besides, I have money.
再说了，我还有钱。
But madam...
但是夫人...
You can't show yourself in public.
你不能在公共场合展示自己。
correct.
正确的。
But it is possible.
但这是可能的。
but...
但...
All major stores in Huangcheng...
皇城各大卖场...
Know who your servant is.
知道谁是你的仆人。
If they...
如果他们...
Go out and shop every day.
每天出去购物。
Adigan Bonus
阿迪甘奖金
my senior.
我的前辈。
Young Master, why didn't you say you would visit?
少爷，你怎么不说要来？
Mother is worried about Hua Chen’s injury.
母亲担心华晨的伤势。
So he asked to get a therapist to check it out.
于是他要求找一位治疗师来检查一下。
difference.
不同之处。
I heard it from my sister-in-law's servant...
我是从嫂子的仆人那里听来的……
That's it for the past few days...
这几天就这样了...
You don't show interest...
你没有表现出兴趣...
Despite suffering serious injuries.
尽管受了重伤。
This is my family's business...
这是我家族的生意...
So you don't have to think about it.
所以你不必考虑它。
Yah...
啊...
great.
伟大的。